All right. What's going on everybody?
Lower Tech here with another video on
how to get better results, specifically
with face detail from Z Image Turbo.
So, the good thing about Z Image Turbo
is that you can generate images at a
really fast rate, right? But, that those
come with its downsides.
So, some of those downsides being that
you're not going to get the same image
quality that you would get from using,
let's say, Z Image Base or a
high parameter
uh model. So, with this workflow, which
I will leave a link to my Discord, where
you can get it for completely free, in
the description. So, make sure you go
there, join the Discord, and you'll find
the workflow in the free workflows
channel.
Um then, once you do that, you're going
to download the workflow, and you're
going to drag it right into your
ComfyUI.
Um whatever you if you're using uh
RunPod, then just drag it into your
browser with your ComfyUI open.
Or if you're using uh local, then just
drag it into your local.
Um okay. So,
the first thing is that
if you have Z Image Turbo already
installed, you have the models
installed, then you won't need
any of these, cuz you already have them.
If you don't,
I will leave a link to another video on
our channel in the description on how
you can get Z Image Turbo installed with
these models, because that is a whole
separate process that you need to do in
order to be able to generate these
images.
So, go watch that if you don't have Z
Image installed at all. If you do, the
only models that you will need to
download are
two very small models. So, the first is
a BBox, and the second is a SAM. So, I
show you exactly how to get these
installed if you don't have them.
All right. So, for demonstration
purposes, I just deleted my uh
SAM model, I think. What did I What did
I delete?
No, I deleted my B box model
from my files, and I'm going to try and
run this,
and
you're going to notice that
it ran, and it generated an image for
me, but only the undetailed face. So,
that's not what I want. I want all of
the detail with the face. So,
see here that there is node that is
glowing red because I don't have the
model installed. So, I'm going to go to
the toggle bottom panel button down here
in the bottom left of your comfy UI, and
I'm going to see here that there's an
error.
Ultra lit detector provider.
Um and then it says value not in list,
model, blah blah blah. You get the
point.
What I've done, conveniently for your
for your convenience's sake for you, is
I put a little markdown right here that
will give you the exact thing that you
need to paste in the Claude. I guess you
could use
Chat GPT or Grok or whatever you use.
Claude's the best, though. Um and you're
going to just replace this put error
message here part with
what is in the chat down here.
I'm going to
copy this,
head over to Claude.
I'm going to paste that in there.
I'm going to come back, and I'm going to
copy the bottom part here,
and put that under the error message.
Send the message here.
And he is going to search the web.
So, he found it. You can
that he's going to give us a terminal
command that we can just put right into
our Jupiter labs, or if you're running
locally, you just put it into your
um
terminal, your local terminal. Whether
you use PowerShell or command prompt,
whatever. Um so, I'm going to copy that.
Going to head over here to my Jupiter
labs.
We're going to open up a new terminal.
And I'm just going to paste that right
in there.
And you'll see that
you've just downloaded whatever models
you're missing. So, if you're missing
more, which might be, you probably will
be. You'll probably also be missing at
this SAM model here, which he will also
help you with if you just
do the same thing for that model.
I'm going to refresh my comfy now, so
that way that the
node recognizes that the model is now
installed.
All right, I have refreshed, and I'm
going to find the D box face right
there. Boom. So, now I have it. All
right. So, few things. One, you want to
load a character Laura. You should have
a character Laura. If you don't, there's
going to be some tweaks that you need to
do specifically to the face detailer
here. If you do not have a character
Laura, and you're just generating images
of whatever, whose ever whatever face
you're describing in your prompts,
then
you want to turn
one, the D noise here
down to
.2 to be safe. Otherwise,
the
detailer will
kind of
develop a mind of its own and recreate
the face of the original image. So,
without a Laura,
you need to turn the D noise down.
I turned that up a little bit, so I'm
going to put that back there. Okay. So,
what you want to do is you want to get a
prompt, be as
specific as possible, um
or don't. You'll get better results with
a better prompt.
Because that is just the way that C
image works is
detailed prompts, better results. Goes
for pretty much everything. So, what I'm
going to do is I'm going to load the
Laura for my character in this node
here. And then I'm also going to load it
for here. You'll see that everything's
color-coded here. Um everything that's
blue is for the undetailed, um unrefined
image that's going to be generated. And
then everything that is yellow here
is going to be for the face detailer.
So, that helps you,
great. If not,
it's pretty simple. Slow
Load your Laura's in both of those. Now,
I'm going to run this and we are going
to check out the results.
While that runs, I uh just want to put a
quick reminder for you guys.
If you are using RunPod and you haven't
not added credits to your account or
added money to your account previously,
just a reminder, you can get $5 for free
and then I get $5 for free if you use my
referral link, which I will leave in the
description of this video. So, free
money. Also, I am running the RTX 4090
for this. You don't really need anything
more than that. This will get your
images generated
pretty fast. All right, so we have a
result and I'm going to show you guys
that in just a second. Just one thing I
want to put out there. If you're have If
you're not getting the results that you
want, there's a few things that I
recommend changing.
One,
don't mess with the case sampler as
much. It's not really that necessary to
do.
But, if you want more detailed facial
features
or less detailed facial features, these
are the things that you can modify to
get those results.
So, the steps here on the face detailer
node,
you can turn the steps down if you want
less detailed face facial features.
You can turn them up if you want more
detailed facial features. The CFG is
probably the number one thing that will
influence the results and give you
stronger realistic facial quality. Um
So, turn the CFG up if you're not
getting
the results that you desire. Other than
that, I wouldn't change too much. You
can mess around with the sampler and
scheduler. Um the denoise, it once you
go past like .7,
the results start to get like
crazy. You It's just not what you want.
Okay, let's look at the uh results now.
So, you're going to see
quite a difference here.
So, I want to point a few things out.
You can see here on the left side, this
is the unrefined image. This is before
the facial uh the face detailer uh
does what it does to the image. So,
you'll see that you kind of get that
really smooth-looking, kind of
plastic-looking
typical AI image generation face.
We can zoom in here. You can see the
lashes are kind of clumped together. You
can see that the
pores are just very nonexistent. The
freckles are very washed and faded out.
And the hair from the
eyebrows, you can't really see like the
the pores or the hair or the um
What are they called? Follicles. There
we go.
Now, if we look on this side, you can
see
we have
way better-looking lashes. Eyebrows, you
can see the hair follicles. You can see
pores. You can see, you know, proper
lighting from the sun reflecting on the
skin the way that it does for, you know,
real images.
Uh you can see here the lips have much
better detail. They look much more
realistic. The skin just looks so much
better. You can even see that you get
better hair quality. You can see
individual strands better. So,
you can see uh on the eyes here, the
eyes have better shape, uh better color,
and the wrinkles are more realistic
looking. Just everything all around.
This
this workflow is probably the best way
to get
Z image base looking results without
having to have the hardware or the space
on your computer or whatever it may be
to actually run Z image base.
This is not an upscaler, so it's not
very resource dependent. It is just an
all around
insane fix for
facial features. So, if you're getting
AI looking, plastic looking results, try
this out and um I
guarantee
you will be very impressed with the
results. And like I said, if you're not
getting the results that you want,
there's a few things you can tweak and
mess around with and I bet within 30
minutes you'll have
way better looking images than you did
30 minutes prior. So, if you like this,
uh please like the video, please
subscribe and if you uh want to join my
Discord to get the workflow,
do that. It's in there. Um
come in, say what's up, uh hang out.
It's brand new Discord, just set it up
and uh we're looking for some, you know,
cool people to hang around and and chat
and talk with. So,
all right guys, that will be it for
today. Thank you and goodbye.